# **JUSTIN JOSE**

## **OBJECTIVE**

To pursue a successful career in the corporate world which nurtures professional growth, rewards innovation, values integrity and acknowledges hard work.

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Senior Executive AR in US Health Care with 5 years and 6 months experience.

- Denial management to get payment from insurance.
- Call insurance representative to know the claim status.
- Check all the denials and take accurate actions to get payment.
- Taking end actions on claims.
- Making corrections on claim including coding corrections to get payment.

Data Entry Operator in US Health Care with 1 year experience.

• Entering data from source documents within given time limits.

#### **WEBTEL India**

Designation: Data Operator, Period: 1year

(17/08/2017 to 18/08/2018), Location: Mangalore.

### Omega Healthcare.

Designation: Executive(AR), period:1 year (19/09/2018 to 30/09/2019), Location: Bangalore.

#### ACN Healthcare.

Designation: Senior Executive (AR), Period: 8 months

(30/10/2019 to 30/06/2020), Location: Bangalore.

#### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Email Id: justinjose094@gmail.com Phone : 9880563892

#### **ADDRESS**

Karanmakalayil(H), Prakanam P.O, Thottupuram, Pathanamthitta(DIST), Kerala-689643

#### **SKILLS**

- Creativity
- Communication
- Problem Solving
- Leadership
- Team Work
- Project Management

#### **HOBBIES**

- Dancing
- Listening to songs

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of birth : 14-03-1994

Gender : Female

Father's Name : Jose Thomas

Mother's Name : Jessy Jose

Nationality : Indian

#### **Thar Worx**

Designation: Senior Executive (AR), Period: 2 years, 5month (06/07/2020 to 03/01/2023), Location: Bangalore.

#### **DFW Medical Practice consultants**

Designation: Senior Biller(AR): Currentlyworking

(03/01/2023 to current), Location: USA

### **Trainings Attended**

UI/UX Design course from Techmindz.

## **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION**

- B.E (CS) from KVG college of Engineering, Mangalore, Karnataka. (from July 2012 to January 2018)
- PUC (PCMB) from SNDP HSS MUTTATHUKONAM, Kerala. (from July 2010 to March 2012)
- 10<sup>th</sup> from ROTARY English Medium High School, Mangalore, Karnataka. (from June 1998 to April 2010)

## **PROJECTS UNDERTAKEN:**

Project name :Sinking of boat.

Description : It is a 3D demonstration with keyboard and mouse interface Which shows the

movement of boat and sinking of the boat.

Final Project : Data Hiding using Steganography.

Description : It is a process of hiding of data inside a file. The data and file can be of any type image,

text, audio or video. It is helpful for the user who needs to send confidential data through

the network.

## **ACHIEVEMENTS:**

- Participated in 'Android App Development Fundamentals' workshop organized by CENSA.
- Attended the training under the 'Infosys Campus Connect Soft Skills Program' at our institution.
- Attended district level singing competition.

- Received Quality Award from Omega Health Care and WEBTEL India for maintaining 100% Accuracy.
- Received Award from Omega Health Care for getting Second Rank in AR Training.

# **LANGUAGES**

English, Kannada, Malayalam, Hindi and Tamil

## **DECLARATION**

<u>I</u> JUSTIN JOSE, do hereby confirm that the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge.

**JUSTIN JOSE**